Can film survive our digital future?
Side by Side is a documentary film directed by Christopher Kenneally.
Since the invention of cinema, the standard format for
recording moving images has been film.
Over the past two decades, a new form of digital filmmaking has
emerged, creating a groundbreaking evolution in the medium.
Keanu Reeves explores the development of cinema and the impact of digital filmmaking via in-depth interviews with Hollywood masters, such as
James Cameron, David Fincher, David Lynch, Christopher Nolan, Martin Scorsese, George Lucas, Steven Soderbergh, and many more.
Self / Host, played by Keanu Reeves.
Self, played by Martin Scorsese.
Self, played by James Cameron.
Self, played by David Fincher.
Self, played by David Lynch.
Self, played by Lars von Trier.
Side by Side is a 2012 American documentary film
directed by Christopher Kenneally.
It was produced by Justin Szlasa and Keanu Reeves.
It premiered at the 62nd Berlin International Film Festival
and it was shown at the Tribeca Film Festival.
The film explores themes of movie business, interview,
cinematographer, filmmaking, documentary filmmaking.
The tone is emotional.